<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[diveLang (David langenmayr)]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[diveLang (David langenmayr)]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/divelang-david-langenmayr/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 00:14:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/divelang-david-langenmayr/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Professional ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f5dd469f-ea52-41aa-b811-0ac190597a06.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/divelang-david-langenmayr/happenigs/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">703f981a-ddac-4f59-b85d-a0155049a8bb</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 00:14:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Educational Philosophy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Educational Philosophy</h1><p>I believe schools should challenge students to excel in the areas of global citizenship, and to promote both cultural acceptance, and environmental stewardship. To challenge our children justly in these areas we need to create teaching/learning spaces that are emotionally safe, intellectually stimulating, and technically exceptional. The concept of global citizenship involves identifying with peoples of differing cultures and creating relationships that share a perspective or worldview. The school and classroom should be emotionally safe areas where relationships and global worldviews are constructed and tested. When schools exhibit diversity in both staffing models and student populations it is easier to achieve a superior level of global citizenship. Children entrusted to educators are unique individuals and deserve a stimulating learning, social, and school environment to aid them in finding their passion and reaching their ultimate potential. I believe that in the art of teaching 90% represents relationship building with the students, and 10% teacher technical skills. Educators are guides that provide the space and access to information sources so that students may discover and practice skills in authentic situations, develop respect for themselves, others, and the natural environment. I envision education as a system that guides our children to their passion through knowledge and use of past, present, and future technologies.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f1ba9726-2bdd-40d8-9a0a-6c4aa37b3495.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/divelang-david-langenmayr/educational-philosophy/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bb599645-2e75-4544-9073-80be98f48236</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 09:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>